Dr. David Ashley White Papers, 1965-2001
University of Houston Libraries
- Audio/Visual Materials, 1973-2000 (Box 34-39)
  - Audio Cassettes (Box 34-38)
    - Anthems for Treble Voices from Paraclete Press, 1996 (Box 38, Cassette 4)
    - Music, June 9, 1991 (Box 38, Cassette 5)
    - Music Only, March 1, 1992 (Box 38, Cassette 6)
  - Video (Box 38)
    - UH Composers Forum, May 7, 1996 (Box 38, Cassette 7)
  - Record Albums (Box 39, Cassette 1-2)
    - David Ashley White/Henry Cowell Mirecourt Trio, TR Records, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Cassette 1)
    - Outstanding Contemporary Composers of Texas, undated (Box 39, Cassette 2)